Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
With their reincarnation finally complete, Licht and his comrades set out for the royal capital to begin their invasion.
Nozel, Noelle, Mimosa, Sora, Kirsch, and N.
With the still unconscious captain in tow, hurry to stop the onslaught.
Someone's attacking that area.
But that's the village!
Stop!
Oh no! Stay back!
Asta and Yuno took a detour and soon discovered that Ha's village, their childhood home, was being threatened by a violent elf possessing a magic knight's body.
Asta! Yuno!
You're really brave, Nash.
Good job! Stay back! It's our turn now!
Crescent Moonsickle!
Four blades!
His mana says it all.
The elf spirit inside him is crying out in pain.
Is it possible? Are the elves asking for help?
Hey, Yuno!
Let's go, Asta!
He's turning into something that's not an elf at all!
We should set him free!
Did he undo the reincarnation magic?
Now that I have this sword...
I can save them!
I cannot save everyone!
Is it possible?
When seems to be nice...
I can save everything else...
Why no?
I cannot lose...
There are all these vessels that I can't do...
I can't do the job...
Ouríssuned song...
Thanks.
Thanks,мы.
And let's let nobody out of you
No!
Do we
Yeah!
What's up with that giant rock in the sky?
I don't believe this
Where did that thing come from?
Oh boy
I think it's finally time for me to have some fun for real
What the hell?
The city's in danger
That's our cue, Vanessa
Okay
Hey, take your own broom, would you?
There's no time to get flustered
We gotta go
I wasn't flustered, I'm just saying
Whatever, just hang on tight, okay?
Here we go, crazy cyclone
Pedal to the metal
I sense elven magic up ahead
It's coming from the north and the south
Since there are two places in danger
Perhaps we should split up
Ready?
Of course
See you at the capital
This ain't right
I was expecting to run into a bad guy here
Instead we find you
Why?
What gives?
Stop that
What, are you like
Stupid?
Talk to us, Luck
Luck who?
Oh right, I remember
I think there was somebody he wanted to see
Was it you two?
Either way, he can't
Because thanks to the reincarnation spell
This body now belongs to me, Rufal
Who's Rufal?
What are you going on about?
That spell is forbidden magic
Huh?
I'm not sure of the details
But some other entity has taken over Luck's body
Who could have done that though?
What?
The Eye of the Midnight Sun?
Probably
Luck and the rest of the Royal Knights
Did infiltrate their base after all
Wait a minute
So that big glowing ball we saw hovering in the sky was
The hideout
Crap
I guess the plan to eliminate those monsters must have fallen through somehow
Hey, you got it
I'm surprised
It turns out you're not as dumb as you look
And by the way
We killed those Royal Knights every last one
Here's a tip
If you decide to get in my way
The same thing will happen to you too
Weird
For some reason my kick went in a different direction
Oh
This must be a spell to protect your friends
It's so interesting
You're trying my patience here, pal
I'll make you feel the burn
Eat this
Explosive scatter
The red thread of fate
Rouge is always on the side of the Black Bulls
So she'll protect Luck
Even though his body is possessed right now
Does your little pet have an off switch?
Because it ain't helping me
Seriously?
If it weren't for Rouge
Luck's last attack would have killed you
Besides
If what he said before was the truth
Then Luck's lying dormant in that body
Yeah, I know
That's why I'm trying to give the guy a wake-up call
And I've got just the thing
I'll use flame magic
Explosive scatter shot
Go!
It's such a simple spell
It'll never make contact
They're gone
I still sense their mana
I call this one
Explosive annihilation scatter shot
It's fast
There's not a spell in the world that can hit me
Which means two pitiful humans like you don't stand a chance
Shut up!
Come on!
You're too slow to dot my attacks
Just give up!
Thanks, Vanessa!
Honestly, you boys are so quick to lose your tempers during a battle
Why don't you let me intervene?
Then again, if you do manage to defeat Luck
Who knows?
He might wake up out of shock
If you say so
Explosive scatter!
Time to show how much you've improved after training with me
Give it a rest, would you?
What does it look like I'm doing?
I told you it won't hit me
Luck and I may have fought together a million times
But he's never seen what I'm about to do next
Time bomb explosive scatter shot
Whether it makes contact or not
It still explodes
Good luck, thousands of them all!
You must be kidding
That spell is nothing
Too easy
You could at least make it a challenge for me
I thought you said these things would explode even if they missed
You wouldn't lie to me, would you?
Or did you run out of magic?
If he's dodging by sensing the mana
Magna can just throw in some regular scatter shots
From this distance, I can't miss
Too bad
I picked up on your mana
Nice trick
But I already knew you had that up your sleeve
And I know how fast you are
Did he just make sure it would explode at that exact moment?
You're definitely not luck
Because he would have figured out
I'm stupid enough to blow myself up, Duke!
You're a wily fella, I'll give you that much
But only luck himself could have seen that coming
And I know how to take a hit
Which is more than I can say for you
Flame magic!
Go get to an exploding fireball!
One more thing
Flame bondage formation
Listen, man, I happen to know luck pretty damn well
You're nothing but an imposter
And that means
You don't know the first thing about him or about me
So come at me all you want
But you'll never win
Now give our squad mate back to us
Right now!
What?
You
I'm sorry
Who can never win?
Think again, human
Now, would you care to explain how you two weaklings plan to defeat me?
I'd just love to hear
Keep on talking
I'll throw as many of these fireballs as I have to until luck wakes up
He vanished
Forget it
You won't put another scratch on me
He's so fast
I can't see him
You slow humans could never catch me at this scene
I thought the guy was a monster before
But this is something else
Looking for me?
Well, here I am
Oh, no
The cat
Controlling the future
No
Controlling fate is more like it
Oh well
Even a cat only has so many lives
And I'm sure that spell really drains your magic reserves, right?
The elves are the ones who were originally blessed by mana
So between you and me
Which one of us do you think will last longer?
Don't tell me you're tired already
I haven't even broken a sweat yet
I warned you about getting in my way
Let me go
Now every human in this kingdom will die
That's the fate you deserve
And we elves will be happy to make it a reality
Shut up
You're free
Not one more word
It doesn't matter to me whether you're an elf or not
Because I'm through talking to you
Luck is the one I want to talk to
So you hurry up and get out of that body
Right now
You hear me?
Luck is mischievous
Always being reckless and causing trouble
But he's still like my little brother
Let go of him
All you humans are selfish traitors
Why should I believe that you care about him?
Don't make me laugh
There's nothing that can undo the reincarnation spell
Especially not whatever flimsy bond you claim to have with this luck person
That disgusting human soul has already been destroyed
Is that right?
Well if that's how it is
Then what are you crying for?
You're acting like someone you're not
But I can tell that you're in there luck
Somewhere
And I want you to know that while you were goofing off
I was working hard and training myself to be stronger
If that pisses you off
Then snap out of it
And fight me already you little moron
That's enough
Luck
If you think you can get rid of us that easily
You've got another thing coming
My red thread of fate has you
And I am never letting go of you
Take control of your body and stop this
No! Shut up!
I won't!
It's not gonna work!
Come on!
Shut your mouth!
Please don't
It's over human!
No!
You think I'd let you hurt them?
Not a chance!
Rouge used up all her power
To trigger a destiny that would bring Asta here
And who are you?
I think you know
But I'll say it as much as it takes
We're luck's friends and fellow magic knights!
Asta
Thank goodness
Friends, huh?
This whole routine is starting to get old
Wait a second
You don't have any magic, do you?
I didn't think it was possible for anyone to be that despised by mana
Yeah, well there's one group who accepts me just the way I am
And they're called the Black Bulls
Luck is part of that group
So you can't have him
You can ramble about friendship all day long
But you still won't be able to keep up with me
You're going to die by your comrade's hands
A human shouldn't be able to match my speed
How's that possible?
Your key is so full of rage that I can read it loud and clear
And this blade will follow you anywhere you go
It can't resist powerful magic like yours
Now I'm annoyed
I'm actually impressed
It's no use
You're no match for my anger
Oh crap
He shouldn't be able to detect me
But his combat sense is off the charts
Hey Magna and Vanessa
Could you guys get me some backup over here?
You bet
What makes you think your attacks will affect me now?
Not only that
This time I've got a handle on how fast you are
You have to know
I can't hold out for long
Better make this count
I've already beat you
You can stop now
He's got no magic so their plan is to hide him from me
Fine then
I'll spread out my mana in all directions until I detect the moment his weapon interrupts it
Found him
And he's headed straight for me
He can't escape now
My rage overpowers everything
There you are
Do it
Here goes
They messed up my timing
Come on
Now
He's wide open
You're strong but our bond is stronger
You lose
Nice going Asta
Keep going Asta
Let's get you out of there
He's got so much power left
You humans are doomed
Just wait and see
You really don't know when to throw in the towel do you punk?
We're not going to give up on our friend
We told you
Stop it
Get your hands off me
Make too much distance
Home
A 追い続けてた夢が
独り歩きになってた
次の道への地図は
どこかに忘れてきた
行くあてすら決めず彷徨った
夜道が少しぼやけた
人生は全長だ そう感じることもある 自分らしくとは何も反対とはない
愛なんて知らない 笑うのも痛い でも本当は強くないよ
歩くべき道をずっと手探りだけで探してる
薔薇を削って тебя無し
水曜りのために自分であって有用
と記憶自体を待ってつけた
愛の好み
I'm not letting anything tear the Black Bulls apart
色々押さない
高級なシフayette